```json
{
  "predicted_order": [
    {
      "position": 1,
      "driver_id": "max_verstappen",
      "reasoning": "Despite the lack of specific 2024 data in the context, Max Verstappen and Red Bull have demonstrated unparalleled dominance in recent seasons and the early part of 2024. His ability to extract maximum performance from the car, coupled with Red Bull's strategic prowess, makes him the overwhelming favorite for victory at any circuit, including the returning Shanghai."
    },
    {
      "position": 2,
      "driver_id": "perez",
      "reasoning": "Sergio Perez benefits from driving the dominant Red Bull machinery. While not consistently matching Verstappen's pace, he is typically the strongest contender for second place, especially on circuits that suit the RB20's characteristics. His experience and consistency should see him secure a strong podium finish."
    },
    {
      "position": 3,
      "driver_id": "sainz",
      "reasoning": "Carlos Sainz has shown exceptional form and consistency when racing in 2024 (based on external knowledge), often outperforming his teammate. Ferrari's car appears to be the closest challenger to Red Bull, and Sainz's strategic intelligence and race craft position him well for a podium finish."
    },
    {
      "position": 
